Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between the Nash Division of the Nash-Kelvinator Corporation and Lodge No. 34 of the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography of African, Asian and Latin American Countries -- Industrial Relations Literature Covering the Period: 1968-1975, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Selected Bibliography of Western European Industrial relations Literature Covering the Period 1968-1976, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Glamour for the Girl with a Job, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Human relations in Supervision, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: 1947 Contracts, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Accounting, Traffic and Plant Contracts, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Supervisory Training Material on Company Policies, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Facts About the Benefit Plan for Bell System Men and Women, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Communicaions Workers of America, Michigan Division 44 and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Agreement Between the Communications Workers of America, Michigan Division 44 and the Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Fepartment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: You Your Job and Your Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Plan of employee representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Yale & Towne Mfg. Co., Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: A History of Standard Oil Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employees Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Joint Committee Employees Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Employees Representation Plan for the Plants of Swift & Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The SOHIO Council Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Social Costs of Instability in Construction: A Preliminary Report, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Representation of Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Plan of Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Plan of Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
    By W.W. Atterbury. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad System, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Experiences of the Pennsylvania Railroad System with Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: An Employee's View of How the Plan of Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad Actually Works, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Annual report 1954, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Partnership of Faith, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: How Do You Sell Architects?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Salaried Position Description, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Non-Contributory Pension Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Salaried Personnel Policie Exempt and Non-Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Records of Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Studebaker Athletic Association, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Instructions for Performance Review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Opportunities for College Men, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Studebaker Spotlight, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Insurance Agreement Between the Studebaker corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, C.I.O, Local No. 5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Insurance Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, C.I.O Local No. 5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Pension Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, Unied Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Pension Plan for Houtly-Rated Emplurees of the Studebaker Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Studebaker Communications Primer, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Agreement Between Studebaker Corporation and UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Pacific Coast review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Onan News, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: News Releases, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Histoy of Studebaker, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Studebaker Handbook for Salaried employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Women for Automotive Maintenance Service, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: War Production Work for Studebaker Dealers, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: United fund Drive, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Opportunities with te Studebaker Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: Wage Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local no. 1555, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 30: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corpoation and he United Automobile Workers of America Local Union #5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 31: Industrial relation Policies, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 32: Accident Investigation and Report, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 33: Apprenticeship Training at Studebaker-Packard in South bend, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 34: Agreement of Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 35: Fringe Benefit Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 36: Newest of the New!, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 37: Your Studebaker Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 38: Your Studebaker Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 39: Contributory Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees of Studebaker-Packard Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 40: Studebaker-UAW Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 41: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 42: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 43: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 44: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 45: Studebaker Dealers in War Production Worl, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 46: Step-by-Step Training of Women, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 47: Employee's handbook, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 48: Agreements Between the Studebaker Corporation and Local 5, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 49: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implemnt Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 50: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 51: How to Stay Safely at Studebaker-Packard, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 52: Group Hospitalization Program for retires Employees of Studebaker-Packard Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 53: Studebaker Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 54: Supplemental Agreements Between Studebaker Packard Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 55: Agreement Between Studebaker-Packard Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 56: How we Work at Studebaker, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 57: Studebaker Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 58: So Help Me!, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 59: Visibility Zero?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 60: Rules of Conduct in Studebaker Plant, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 61: What is a Credit Union?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)